<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ctf on /home/</title>
    <link>/tags/ctf/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ctf on /home/</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/ctf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>come ctf with me #3 - metactf 2020 part 1 - password here please</title>
      <link>/posts/metactf2020_passwordhereplease/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/metactf2020_passwordhereplease/</guid>
      <description>MetaCTF 2020 - Password Here Please For this CTF, I&#39;ll upload the challenges I found interesting as individual write-ups. I don&#39;t know how many I&#39;ll do (time is a bastard) but I&#39;ll try and get at least a few. For this challenge specifically, I have the source code down below, as well as my full script in the tl;dr.
Description I forgot my bank account password! Luckily for me, I wrote a program that checks if my password is correct just in case I forgot which password I used, so this way I don&#39;t lock myself out of my account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>come ctf with me #2 - acictf - pt 1</title>
      <link>/posts/acictf2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/acictf2020/</guid>
      <description>Army Cyber Institute Capture the Flag On the ball this year about starting right away, so let&#39;s get right in
Skip the Tutorial - 0 no thanks
First Rule - 1 So this one is just getting us familiar with what a flag looks like; in this case, ACI{this_is_a_flag}
Distant Socializing - 2 This one&#39;s easy, just join an appropriate group (NCO, in my case), and you get a flag: ACI{welcome_to_the_club}</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>come ctf with me #1 - kringlecon 2019 - pt 2</title>
      <link>/posts/kringlecon2019pt2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/kringlecon2019pt2/</guid>
      <description>Mongo Pilfer - CranberryPi After the last CranPi, I took a week break from the ctf to focus on work, but with the arrival of the weekend and completion of some overdue errands, I was ready to go. To get into the swing of things, I decided to start cleaning up the other CranberryPis I dutifully noted before, starting with Holly Evergreen&#39;s in the NetWars Continuous room (where I made a cameo!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>come ctf with me #1 - kringlecon 2019 - pt 1</title>
      <link>/posts/kringlecon2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/kringlecon2019/</guid>
      <description>Kringlecon 2: Turtle Doves! I&#39;m starting Kringlecon a day late this year, but I&#39;m hoping to be able to at least get as far as I got last year. This time, I plan on documenting my findings, and I&#39;ll be updating this as I go. My plan is for this to be one big post, almost in a journal/gamefaqs style.
Escape Ed - CranberryPi This one is easy, but I did have to google since i&#39;m unfamiliar with ed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>